<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Imran&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Imran&#39;s Site</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:15:22 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ad Free Alternatives on Android and iOS</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/ad-free-alternatives-android-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 19:21:48 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/ad-free-alternatives-android-ios/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t you hate it when a video player starts showing ad while you are watching a movie? Or while navigating in your music player to play your favorite music? Well, fear no more! Here are the apps I use (you should use too) on daily basis, which are completely free with no ad whatsoever.
Video Player (VLC) Replaces: MX Player, MX Player Pro
VLC is a name you may seen in your PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a horizontal scroll section with HTML,CSS and JS</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/create-horizontal-scroll-section-html-css-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:15:22 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/create-horizontal-scroll-section-html-css-js/</guid>
      <description>Horizontal Section A horizontal section is a section which spreads left to right. It is very elegant and takes less space and can show more data.
Making a horizontal section Create three files, index.html, index.css and index.js. Name theme to your liking. Just be sure to link them properly in the index.html file. Then open the index.html file in your favorite code editor. Add the following code to the index.html file:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differences Between Ssg and Spa</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/differences-between-ssg-and-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 19:26:52 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/differences-between-ssg-and-spa/</guid>
      <description>SSR SSR means Server side rendering. In this mode, the requested page gets rendered on the server.
Building in SSR is fast compared to SSG when dealing with many pages. However it is slower than SSG in client side. SEO can be a little tricky but can do its job when done properly. Useful for app/sites that depends on everchanging data or interactive elements.
SSG SSG means Static site generation. The site is rendered once during build time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
