<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ad Free Alternatives on Android and iOS</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/post/ad-free-alternatives-on-android-and-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 19:21:48 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/post/ad-free-alternatives-on-android-and-ios/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t you hate it when a video player starts showing ad while you are watching a movie? Or while navigating in your music player to play your favorite music? Well, fear no more! Here are the apps I use (you should use too) on daily basis, which are completely free with no ad whatsoever.
Video Player (VLC) Replaces: MX Player, MX Player Pro
VLC is a name you may seen in your PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Umbrella</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/bring-your-umbrella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/bring-your-umbrella/</guid>
      <description>An app made mainly for getting the days with high chances of rainfall. It also gives the weather forecast of next 5 days.
Features Days with highest rainfall, highest and lowest temperature. Chances of rainfall Amount of rainfall Chart of rainfall chances Chart of highest and lowest temperature This app was made using ReactJS and CSS. For generating charts, Recharts was used.
You can find the app by clicking here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Note App</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/take-note-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/take-note-app/</guid>
      <description>A simple app to take and save your note. It uses browsers&amp;rsquo; local storage to save your data.
This app was made using ReactJS and Material UI.
You can find the app by clicking here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watchnext</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/watchnext/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/watchnext/</guid>
      <description>An app which fetch data from TMDB API and display the movies and shows which are trending and popular in the world.
Features Movies and shows which are trending and popular in the world. Search for movies and shows. add to watchlist of movies and shows. Add to favorite list of movies and shows. This app was made using SvelteKit and CSS.
You can find the app by clicking here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differences Between Ssg and Spa</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/post/differences-between-ssg-and-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 19:26:52 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/post/differences-between-ssg-and-spa/</guid>
      <description>SSR SSR means Server side rendering. In this mode, the requested page gets rendered on the server.
Building in SSR is fast compared to SSG when dealing with many pages. However it is slower than SSG in client side. SEO can be a little tricky but can do its job when done properly. Useful for app/sites that depends on everchanging data or interactive elements.
SSG SSG means Static site generation. The site is rendered once during build time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog With Svelte</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/blog-with-svelte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/blog-with-svelte/</guid>
      <description>This blog was made using SvelteKit and Contentful.
You can find the blog by clicking here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dummy Text Generator</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/dummy-text-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/blog/portfolio/dummy-text-generator/</guid>
      <description>An app to generate dummy text. Useful for testing purposes. It uses a free remote API to generate text.
The app was made using ReactJS and Material UI.
You can find the app by clicking here</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
