<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Imran&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Imran&#39;s Site</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imranmollajoy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ad Free Alternatives on Android and iOS</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/ad-free-alternatives-android-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 19:21:48 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/ad-free-alternatives-android-ios/</guid>
      <description>Tired of dealing with ads and pop-ups in your video and music players, or when reading documents on your phone? Try using ad-free apps listed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Detailed Article on Fungi</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/detailed-article-fungi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 15:11:05 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/detailed-article-fungi/</guid>
      <description>The Role of Fungi in the Ecosystem #Fungi are a diverse group of eukaryotic organisms that are distinct from animals, plants, and other forms of life. They are non-photosynthetic and typically characterized by the presence of chitin in their cell walls. Fungi are found in a wide range of environments, including soil, water, and other organisms, where they play important roles in the ecosystem by breaking down organic matter and aiding in nutrient cycling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pros of Using Open Source Softwares</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/pros-of-using-open-source-softwares/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 21:25:05 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/pros-of-using-open-source-softwares/</guid>
      <description>Open source software is software that is distributed with a license that allows users to freely use, modify, and distribute the software. Unlike proprietary software, which is owned and controlled by a single company or person, open source software is developed and maintained by a community of volunteers who are dedicated to improving the software and making it as useful and user-friendly as possible.
The concept of open source software originated in the late 1980s, when a group of software developers began collaborating on a project to create a free, open source operating system called Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Umbrella</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/bring-your-umbrella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/bring-your-umbrella/</guid>
      <description>An app made mainly for getting the days with high chances of rainfall. It also gives the weather forecast of next 5 days.
Features # Days with highest rainfall, highest and lowest temperature. Chances of rainfall Amount of rainfall Chart of rainfall chances Chart of highest and lowest temperature This app was made using ReactJS and CSS. For generating charts, Recharts was used.
You can find the app by clicking here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Note App</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/take-note-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/take-note-app/</guid>
      <description>A simple app to take and save your note. It uses browsers&amp;rsquo; local storage to save your data.
This app was made using ReactJS and Material UI.
You can find the app by clicking here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watchnext</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/watchnext/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/watchnext/</guid>
      <description>An app which fetch data from TMDB API and display the movies and shows which are trending and popular in the world.
Features # Movies and shows which are trending and popular in the world. Search for movies and shows. add to watchlist of movies and shows. Add to favorite list of movies and shows. This app was made using SvelteKit and CSS.
You can find the app by clicking here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a horizontal scroll section with HTML,CSS and JS</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/create-horizontal-scroll-section-html-css-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:15:22 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/create-horizontal-scroll-section-html-css-js/</guid>
      <description>Horizontal Section #A horizontal section is a type of layout in which the content is arranged from left to right, rather than from top to bottom. This design can be elegant and visually appealing, and it can also save space by allowing more content to be displayed on the screen at once. Horizontal sections are commonly used in web design to create menus, galleries, or other types of content that can be easily scrolled through by the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differences Between SSG and SPA</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/differences-between-ssg-and-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 19:26:52 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/post/differences-between-ssg-and-spa/</guid>
      <description>Introduction #Server-side rendering (SSR) and static site generation (SSG) are two different approaches to web development that are used for different purposes. In this article, we will explore the differences between SSR and SSG, their respective advantages and disadvantages, and how to decide which approach is best for your specific project.
What is Server-side rendering (SSR)? #Server-side rendering (SSR) is a technique in which a web page is rendered on the server in response to a user&amp;rsquo;s request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog With Svelte</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/blog-with-svelte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/blog-with-svelte/</guid>
      <description>This blog was made using SvelteKit and Contentful.
You can find the blog by clicking here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dummy Text Generator</title>
      <link>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/dummy-text-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imranmollajoy.github.io/portfolio/dummy-text-generator/</guid>
      <description>An app to generate dummy text. Useful for testing purposes. It uses a free remote API to generate text.
The app was made using ReactJS and Material UI.
You can find the app by clicking here </description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
